Seungone Kim

My main research goal is to understand the inherent limitations of large language models (LLMs) and to enhance their capabilities for more effective deployment in real-world scenarios.

Specifically, I am interested in (1) improving the **reasoning & planning** abilities of LLM agents [C2, C4, O1]; (2) ensuring LLMs to truly follow human instructions via **alignment methods** (e.g., Instruction Tuning and RLHF) [C3, P3]; (3) understanding the properties and behaviors of LLMs through **fine-grained evaluation** [P1, P2]; (4) grounding LMs to share **commonsense knowledge** as humans do [C1].

Education

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Seoul, Korea

M.S. in Artificial Intelligence

March 2023 - Present

Advisor: Minjoon Seo

Yonsei University

Seoul, Korea

B.S. in Computer Science

March 2018 - February 2023

Publications

Peer-Reviewed Conference Papers....

• [C4] The CoT Collection: Improving Zero-shot and Few-shot Learning of Language Models via Chain-of-Thought Fine-Tuning

The 2023 Conference on Empirical Methods in Natural Language Processing (EMNLP 2023) **Seungone Kim***, Sejune Joo*, Doyoung Kim, Joel Jang, Seonghyeon Ye, Jamin Shin, Minjoon Seo [Paper] [Code]

- [C3] Exploring the Benefits of Training Expert Language Models over Instruction Tuning The 40th International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML 2023) Joel Jang, Seungone Kim, Seonghyeon Ye, Doyoung Kim, Lajanugen Logeswaran, Moontae Lee, Kyungjae Lee, Minjoon Seo [Paper] [Code]
- [C2] CoTEVer: Chain of Thought Prompting Annotation Toolkit for Explanation Verification
 The 17th Conference of the European Chapter of the Association for Computational Linguistics (EACL 2023)

Seungone Kim, Se June Joo, Yul Jang, Hyungjoo Chae, Jinyoung Yeo [Paper] [Code]

[C1] Mind the Gap! Injecting Commonsense Knowledge for Abstractive Dialogue Summarization
 Proceedings of the 29th International Conference on Computational Linguistics (COLING 2022)
 Seungone Kim*, Se June Joo*, Hyungjoo Chae*, Chaehyeong Kim*, Seungwon Hwang, Jinyoung Yeo [Paper] [Code]

Preprints....

[P1] Prometheus: Inducing Fine-grained Evaluation Capability in Language Models
 Under Review at ICLR 2024 & NeurIPS 2023 Instruction Following Workshop
 Seungone Kim*, Jamin Shin*, Yejin Cho*, Joel Jang, Shayne Longpre, Hwaran Lee, Sangdoo Yun, Seongjin Shin, Sungdong Kim, James Thorne, Minjoon Seo
 [Paper] [Code]

- [P3] Multi-objective Reinforcement Learning from Personalized Human Feedback
 Planning for Submission at ICML 2024
 Joel Jang, Seungone Kim, Bill Yuchen Lin, Yizhong Wang, Jack Hessel, Luke Zettlemoyer, Hannaneh Hajishirzi, Yejin Choi, Prithviraj Ammanabrolu
 [Paper] [Code]

Research Experience

NAVER AI Lab Seongnam, Korea

Research Internship at Language Research Team

Mar 2023 – Present

I have lead a research project, exploring whether open-sourced LMs could replace GPT-4 evaluation [P1].

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Seoul, Korea

Research Internship at Language and Knowledge Laboratory

Jul 2022 - Feb 2023

I participated in a research project building Expert language models, overcoming the weakness of a single Instruction-tuned LM [C3].

Seoul National University

Seoul, Korea

Research Internship at Language and Data Intelligence Laboratory

Sep 2021 - Jun 2022

I have participated in a research project building a multilingual language model for low-resource languages via continual cross-lingual pre-training.

Invited Talks

Commonsense Knowledge Consortium 1st Workshop

Seoul, Korea

Presented paper accepted at COLING 2022[C1]

July 2022

Host: Prof. II Chul Moon(KAIST), Chanyoung Park(KAIST), Jinyoung Yeo(Yonsei), Seungwon Hwang(SNU), Joseph Lim(KAIST), Jonghyeon Choi (Yonsei)

Yonsei University Al Workshop

Seoul, Korea

Presented paper accepted at COLING 2022[C1]

Presented paper accepted at EACL 2023[C2]

October 2022

Host: Prof. Jonghyeon Choi (Yonsei)

Innovation Session Series

Frankfurt, Germany

June 2023

Host: Laux Michael (SAP)

Services

O Conference Reviewer: EACL 2023, EMNLP 2023

Conference Workshop Reviewer: NeurIPS 2023 (Instruction Following WS)

Secondary Reviewer: ACL 2023

Mentoring

O Juyoung Suk: B.S. Student, KAIST (July 2023 - Present)

Teaching Experience & Extracirricular Experience

Korea Army Augmented to US Army (KATUSA)

United States Army Garrison Humphreys

January 2019 – August 2020

I have worked as a translator and a Senior Katusa for Chief Warrant Officers flying Chinook Helicopters across the Peninsula, serving for General Robert B. Abrams, the 25th Commander of U.S. Forces Korea.

Samsung Dream Class

Samsung Welfare

Mentor

March 2022 - February 2023

I have participated in the Dream Class program as a Mentor, organized by Samsung in Korea. I have taught Python programming to middle-school students including object-oriented programming, machine learning with Numpy and Pytorch, and data visualization with Seaborn.